card.com 2014-08-24

# Privacy Policy | CARD.com

### Your account is issued and operated by The Bancorp Bank and is governed by The Bancorp Bank’s privacy practices.

Facts:  | 

#### What Does The Bancorp Do With Your Personal Information?  
  
---|---  
Why?  |  Financial companies choose how they share your personal information. Federal law gives consumers the right to limit some, but not all, sharing. Federal law also requires us to tell you how we collect, share and protect your personal information. Please read this notice carefully to understand what we do.   
What?  |  The types of personal information we collect and share depend on the product or service you have with us. This information can include: 

  * Social Security Number and income 
  * Account balances and transaction history 
  * Credit history and credit scores 

When you are no longer our customer, we continue to share your information, as described in this notice.   
How?  |  All financial companies need to share customers’ personal information to run their everyday business. In the section below, we list the reasons financial companies can share their customers’ personal information, whether The Bancorp shares your information, and whether you can limit this sharing.   
Reasons we can share your personal information |  Does The Bancorp Share? |  Can you limit this sharing?   
---|---|---  
**For our everyday business purposes -** Such as to process your transactions, maintain your account(s), respond to court orders and legal investigations, or report to credit bureaus  |  Yes  |  No   
**For our marketing purposes -** To offer our products and services to you  |  Yes  |  No   
**For joint marketing with other financial companies** |  No  |  We don't share   
**For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes -** information about your transactions and experiences  |  No  |  We don't share   
**For our affiliates everyday business purposes -** Information about your creditworthiness  |  No  |  We don't share   
**For nonaffiliates to market to you** |  No  |  We don't share   
What we do How does The Bancorp protect my personal information?  |  To protect your personal information from unauthorized access and use, we use security measures that comply with federal law. These measures include computer safeguards and secured files and buildings. We also limit access to information to those employees for whom access is necessary.   
---|---  
How does The Bancorp collect my personal information?  |  We collect your personal information when, for example, you: 

  * open an account or apply for a loan 
  * pay your bills or make a wire transfer 
  * provide account information 

We also collect your personal information from others, such as credit bureaus, affiliates, or other companies.   
Why can’t I limit all sharing?  |  Federal law gives you the right to limit only: 

  * sharing for affiliates’ everyday business purposes – information about your creditworthiness 
  * affiliates from using your information to market to you 
  * sharing for nonaffiliates to market to you 

State laws and individual companies may give you additional rights to limit sharing.   
Definitions Affiliates  |  Companies related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and nonfinancial companies. 

  * Our affiliates include financial companies such as The Bancorp Bank and Bancorp Card Services Inc. 

---|---  
Nonaffiliates  |  Companies not related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and nonfinancial companies. 

  * The Bancorp does not share your information with nonaffiliates. 

Joint marketing  |  A formal agreement between nonaffiliated financial companies that together market financial products or services to you. 

  * The Bancorp does not jointly market. 

##  Questions? 

Call us toll-free at 888-255-5962, or email us at support@card.com, or visit us at www.card.com.
